This video will show how the game works, so let's get started.
As you can see here, it shows instructions,
a grid with the asterisks, a timer showing the time elapsed,
and the amount of unmatched cards remaining. And this is how the game asks for coordinates,
say i want row 1, column 1. It's asking me for a row number,
so i press 1 and enter. And column number, I press 1,
enter. It hides a card. And then, if I want to, it will ask me for second card
want to reveal. So I want row 3, column 1. So i write 3, 1
and [it] matches. And as you just heard, it play a sound when you match
the cards. But if I don't match a card, this will
happen. It will just say "No match, try again.". And then you try
again. If you do not write 1,
2, 3 or 4 for a coordinate, you will get an error. So assume
I write [row] 5, [column] 5, you'll get message saying that the coordinate is invalid.
So [this would] also be a problem if you write 0, this would also be invalid.
So any number that's either 0, or 5 and above,
the program will not work.
You will be asked if you want to play again.
So if I do want to play again, I'll press 'yes', and the whole game resets to what
it was before. So I just do the same thing as usual. And if I don't want to play
again, I just press 'end' to end the game, and the program exits
and that's pretty much it.